SAMRUDDHI CHINCHWADKAR

HUMAN RESOURCES EXECUTIVE

Address : F-34 2nd floor, lavkush awas vihar,

sukhliya, Indore, M.P.

Email: samruddhichinchwadkar081@gmail.com

About Me

Hello! My name is Samruddhi, I recently worked in a startup company as a Human Resource Executive and i was the only HR who handle all the functions of a particular department. I am confident in managing the human resources in a company to sustain the most professional working environment. I left that organization to gain more knowledge and achieve proficiency in a same field.

Personal Info

Birthdate: 03/04/2000

Language: English, Hindi, Marathi

Phone: 6260335819

Experience

Visko HR Private Limited 2023-2024 Human Resources Executive

Mandot Securities Private Limited

HR Executive intern

Tata Consultancy Services 2021-2022

Business Process Associate

Teleperformance 2019-2021

Data Entry Specialist



Personal Traits

Ease of communication
Friendliness
Approachability
Cooperativeness
Creativity

Education

Sage University 2020-2022

Masters' in MBA HR and Production
Operation Management
Shri Cloth Market Girls Commerce
College 2017-2020

Bachelor's in B.com with Computer Science